The Yeah sure yeah yeah you're
in the urban.
Poor Are you. Serious.
We're all
a into your and just are you.
Hearing
a is itself. A job.
You will world is full of
danger Galloway in your
honor you don't think it
was dangerous if you.
Were or you know I. Am
yourself for all you see
you're in the if you're if
you're in the world and you get
a car is shall. We say or an
eerie
eerie.
Little. The in the doorway
the window the door.
The floor.
Yes yes. If
yes
you smile
Yes
you see.
You.
Use she. Pushes you
just to show Miss also that
you see Thank you sir.
Yes. Yes
yes yes yes but it's just got
a message for me yes sir thank you thank
you. Thank you.
For. All you.
You you. You.
You so on much this way you.
Thank you for two for being on
what you were supposed to
be trying to write you.
Trouble right there.
About the church. Claimed. To wash.
For it's
a dog is trained to lead. Dog you dog are
four legged animals. We're selling fine.
Hello honey oh hello girlie pick
up anything for you. But aren't
Jen No not a thing. In
the day. It's been such
a day oh day to day.
Things just don't day.
Actually mother man who really was it was
he met us well before the anybody but
himself. No good Did you hear me and
hear me good you know what day this is
today. Tuesday says Tuesday.
What happened two years ago
the day I want to two years ago and
maybe I can tell you trying to fix what
happened. Oh I just have to mention
it now you're spoiled it all
I'm sorry darling. It's not that I want
anything excluded or you know what he's
always saying what kind of
a healer what I forget my own wedding
anniversary. It's just that all text I want.
Is
a can't. Know. That it
can be convertible. This
is my anniversary to. What you
get from me I'm wearing it.
The next line might be you know as you
know the old you got the furniture for the
babies so thank you you. Don't need my
present cat like you did last year and.
Then you know the you know I. Had. The
right to.
Go away.
Thank. You Lou.
You better go home to mama.
If you.
Say I help you sir yes. I'd
like something nice for
a lady something special. Charming little
number twenty nine ninety five the
lace is all handmade. It's for
my wife. And when married she's about.
She's got the kind of shape the world should
be and that's about right I'll take it
differently do you have
a card over there sir thank you. Thank
you.
Everything that attacked me so.
Your dog didn't want to. Take
a valium with you have you any idea how
much damage is done to you what is this
season my dog doesn't even begin to visualize
for you crazy animals saw the stars
before my life that my full
if you. Will don't. You know
you don't belong to me yet the yet.
While you're gone home. You.
Yes.
I had this night out you stole gift from
under my arm and I was crossing the street
the pretty big crowd when the some
stranger not the package out of my arm and
before I could pick it up by the media take
it and. If you try to I'm so that you.
Like Tori when you stay
out of this. Place money.
Yet believe it or not you says how it
happened I was in the store say that I just
spoke if you would if I'm like you like I'm
for you when some strange don't believe
you the total stranger. The you
you see.
The other. High end of.
The of honey before you jump
a complete. YOU
THANK YOU for the price
you're ready to know what.
Are you telling the Such
a little. You.
Have another one all right but.
You know what this stuff
does to me. But I trust you.
First we have to wait out
a bunch of free feeders and drinkers
mostly your mother's friends and our
anniversary and we have to wait after Idol
she goes to bed as like before we were
married and all we had was much
a lucky. Push now. So I'd only
just send
a will you be saying some day every day for
two years now so we're still living in
her house in five minutes we could find
a place of our own. Thank you just don't
believe her love was after all she is my
mother. But find us
a place and extra place we
could sneak off to once in
a while if. You can afford
a place of our own. I'm doing
pretty good now. I'll do better.
For you when people get married
because they want to be together.
With company together is. Such
a difference we went together here or
somewhere else so long as we're together.
Yes. You think you live
a little more live.
You yes.
You're you. Literally
this yes the rule in
the theater yes. You're
literally.
The only look at him this is think you.
Can do little kids. Ever
think of that. Within
a minute I said oh yes he wants to play
he well I want to sleep. Needed to
give it
a status. Truly I'll throw
him. Still he's only
a pompous baby practically he wants
to get acquainted Well I want to.
At three am It's.
He is so me
a puppy. The
.
Come on come on come on. I
got to get to work in the
morning you sleep in the kitchen
down below under the stove.
The reasonable. It's after three. I
sleep up here. See.
See.
Who's things trembling. Are they very.
Little going to leave me
alone tonight not for
a single minute. Why
God. What's the matter. Please
also don't you come by.
For just
a few seconds I close my eyes you know
that you are trying to get shut for things
like that. That I sleep in
a dark bed like you were all night I stay
here all night watch because things go
wrong most likely they're waiting for
a lot of people to be around before they
make the contact. With the nearest.
Six blocks. You watch when I get back.
Go away the to.
The.
Land all. The of.
You must belong to somebody.
The best will terrier.
My child cried all night to find her please
return reward Hollywood nine six eight
five.
Yes you have. Older. Cheney here.
All of my four babies crying your eyes out
you see your dog followed me home last
night and. This may sound
crazy to you but my.
Mother was. My mother in law well I
you know how mother the laws are.
For when you bring. Hearing him we've got
a dog. Hunt she was on the square on
top.
Sorry George Don't trouble yourself
so. I can send for the. No no
no I'm going to bring him to you myself
then I can tell my wife it all ran away or
something and get her another
one and see. It so that is it.
Will be no question about a reward
after all children and dogs I was
a kid myself. Get into as soon as I can
sometime today certainly Mr Jonas.
Five five enough to construct
a good life. Good money mother.
It's got you up and about so early Someone
has to clean up your friend someone else
to get effect first tell you needn't bother
I can get my own for the dog naturally
.
Nice stuff. This. Fire Chief.
Has names are just SO case
named in that. But as night.
Would give me Sunday feeding in the basin
I did not feed it to any stone would you
deliberately put it where he could get
it you want to make him vicious. Di
deliberately did not deliberately any for
you to come home to raise your voice to
me this is my house let me remind you. Of
what is going on they are just feeding
the hindmost facing the dog oh you bet
if the little fat outside did not have
stolen the bacon that is ridiculous I know
you learned them just put thank you Dolly.
You ought to know better than to get
a little bowl and roll Thank you Ted I said
still making vicious foods won't be in
the new high so he's hot all
over and I'd better take him to
a vet for distemper shots or whatever
kind of shots out ahead after all what we
know about him for sure oh OK comes that
you really think you don't know what just
make sure I did that for
eyes. Stay on my side.
Is my gift to you it is my responsibility
what is my responsibility besides
watching that is start getting acquainted.
But don't think I better walk around the
block maybe and now everyone would have
taken them out when I go shopping and I
told them I know I don't take them.
Before money was.
Oh John let's not yet but he called it so
they delivered bringing the don't here
said he was having trouble getting the
model white man's wife want to stop by and
explained You've got to get back to
your oh you know making problems out of
nothing. Oh jeez even you to
laugh. Oh no I'm falling Oh I know
it's kind of some phony trial. So I say
competition nothing to worry about on. You
know your fat head you know me holding
up. On.
Saturday.
The the.
The on the.
Right. So we on this one of course
he's yours. But she promised me if you
walk in tonight. She said
I was using the term. I
am sorry she named him that my wife that
is you need to march in because when I
turn into the circumstances we don't know
his real name so who's watching but I
mean you thought oh. Well I'll get Archie
to without fail tonight tell me what you
read away or something and get her number
to watch what's the matter we will show
well absolutely nothing to do
a great little fellow but naturally if he
belongs to you it's official Oh no that's
very kind of you little boy well what about
your child you said over the phone she
was crying right at the start and I said
oh my god it wrong John but how can you
tell with that.
Operator I want
a policeman. You.
Play board Sergeant O'NEILL I
want to pull them up now. I
want you all on me. Was about.
What you what you asked me
to. FACE IF. I don't hang
up I wish I had or you
really are I don't want freedom.
You need. My.
Apologies.
Address on Iraq.
If you.
Let the other.
The vote. That you give it.
Give it to me the one that you
so much care for that it was
a lot of him to step on two fronts and I
don't want to you know I'm sure on you
you killed him yes quite right
Ryan and you always killed
you know all Germans was the only one we
knew you would have led us to the US right
away to our shores I want it all I'm
a. Tell me they tell me everything
just as it happened I got
it why did John this time I come over to
chat my way the staff was pretty wiped
from done then I'd lied
about it that I ain't got
a scruple and he goes on about
some god of this this must
a lot of cities to all five of the faith
counties wiped out is always the I'm
interested in this stuff yes I thank
you I kid you know I've just found
a job that John is much to last an advertised
for the church said he added but he
didn't abt said tonight he did have
a good go back to wait for.
Go back to the home of cops
you know killing two I never heard of any
knocked off childish screwball I got rid
of I kind of was the wrong
dog you fool D.N.A.
And then I was dumb enough. To come
alone as dog was trained to go to
a certain place I wanted out
of me when it is that I'm
a convent and my cats are shut up so
you will never do they will never do.
We need this. We need this dog to make the
tram so. Who is this screwball want to.
I don't remember even give me his
car he was a state now he was
a general post funny I can call it cause
I go and get it you call the police to
pick up the body and stop dying if you're
going to the advantage because as. Oh
gross drove up. To. You.
So I could see some kid
restaurant all done. You go son.
We have the same. Address some Tell us
a little bit. Oh sure we go why are you.
Actually do you wait. OK you
want to go that way only so low why.
Are you so you.
Know not what you told.
Us not. To do you.
Like. Why you.
Would. You say all right
all right. Yet you had
a white. Where
you. Had been turning around in my
mind. And I think you are right she.
We don't just. Let yourself
be back so you wait why why
did you make all this
and all your right. Ha.
Ha ha. Ha right.
But I don't want to talk. You.
Know.
I'm. Sorry I'm late but
a. Ha ha oh what are you
two boys just cooked up.
To go to your dad's come from the minute
I got him. I never stirred out and there
you stood I say what is this
a pearl Where else would I be if not in my
office where all Cindy. Then what could
I get you there six times i Phone between
two and five thirty are you and I look
here are you. Stay right
there I'll get back to you.
Yes best identity as there always
is that you have one swallow.
The police. Say what you mean.
But that you yes you know Mr Jonas
Jonas No Oh yes no he Mr John this
is why I don't really know him I met him
for the first time today at his apartment
Yes What did you say about Bob what about
him. About what Danny is yours yes I gave
it to him that church we found goodness
pain he's dead or our largest.
Nada you mixed up the other day I knew
some days the others. Want to share you
know Danny for the whole I know what she
knows change knows everything she's my
mother in law Yeah I've had
a couple myself who don't want you in the
day all right ladies all right leave us
have
a word with Mr Denny alone.
Thank you all promised
and Jonas such a nice fellow
so generous you. Give me
a glass bowl in the back.
All right Jenny. About
a dog show this lost
a dog so I found one that fits what he
followed me home and well sort of became an
anniversary present for my wife Deborah
for the love of Mike don't tell her that
her mother never let me hear the end of it
sounds fishy to me since you bothered to
look at simple Jones put an ad in the paper
I thought this was him so I called him
to tell him what happened back and
just as soon as I could take him for
a walk Jonas and then to know the dog this
one Jonas's dog only has not shown this
is the piano let me show you this morning's
post probably be utilized tell OK Let's
show what the you. Know
if you. Do you. Like
the know what you. Did you get
what you saw why don't you play.
Yet. What I bet. You see.
It's the only way you
want all right it like
a good look at this generation. He's wanted
every country over night and Charlie OK
last heard from me was in the can and
perish the face when I'm and I want to now
get out and bring him in you'll kill all
Rapoport. But not all of us and why should
you listen to what is just another I
write tight bias but I want to let this
product Jonas Alright come on Beta get out
the door and what are you in charge here
I cherish service what kind of an apartment
you run anyway by trying to explain to
these two cards that I own the dog but let
me show you that just because I try to
return as
a less. Serious Welsh Terrier
faces that life that I found
just because some fellow got murdered is
no excuse it or not I am show to cherish
and out of my child cry all night find its
way to drug free water to tell identical
powers to the same address I just
hated the title of. Bad enough.
To actual towers I don't get it.
And I've told you and told you No you'll
admit when you stop but remember he didn't
literally anyone like you but he told the
old all motorists incommunicado That's
why do you know the plane took
a little brain and I'll kill him
absolutely crush every bone in his hand.
What does and what do you have
a joint custody to the high point you only
need to know why you guilty that what
you do to the United States LOL is Lucent
tell me everything that I lose why did
you do it at home don't you I'm trying
to understand Take it easy and it wasn't
anything I tell you I'm not saying
it all. I think Oh. I think he says.
So what do you do murder that I
don't know somebody a minute for
a minute do you weigh because I met him
and talked to him for a minute I mean
a lot of people routine checkup man
murdered that Yes QUESTION And you all are
involved mother naturally
murders somebody every day.
What's with her. She told she was
going to I hate New York the just the
same I'll tell you you're welcome when.
You say. By the way it was
a sleepy. Three chairs Florida
only for the evening. The modern
art collection. Which is so modern
the you. Are showing me
joy. When your mother
going on about justice being
minutes. But the best.
Thing the by.
Little. A little on the.
Right from.
Description of. What it might.
Mean is this John. They
don't mention which.
One of them.
Knew me. And the case.
The all. Thank you.
Thank you. The you thank you.
The you're. The on
the phone.
Hello. You. Know anybody
whole few.
You know you
a whole bunch. Of few
I'd thank your pardon sir. I hope
I'm not disturbing you use so I
knocked see the door was
open so I came in Yes
sir it's about your advertisement
for the don't you last
see
it slice Mr Tillotson but
you're supposed to be thank you
for THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK
YOU
FOR
.
I'm. Told. Police.
You know Mrs Downey nothing.
To talk. So it's after two
so maybe you've been
a little delayed Why don't you
just go back to bed. Their
arms and. Then. She's probably only on
a bender.
What did I tell you. Who's. And just
where have you been all this time I knew
that you were going to be back in sixty
minutes I. Took a walk here took
a walk I walked for hours
trying to paint. You could
you point if you suddenly decided to have
a role in the gutter
do you. Not know I I'm
upset that you learn
about me said expecting
a totally motivated to please tell me they
found your body body or say last and I
always say there's a bend in the way shape
not that he'll tell you anything but
a big fat lie I've never seen
a man Oh God Oh wait. Now I'm
going to be spoken to like fed
by my own daughter in my own house. Oh
shut up those are no solutions to most.
Of them so I have little still like you I
know with her around all the time it's
murder for the word stuff the it's not
that it to me is that is there anything
wrong with the old. I mean
certainly I'm so bored and so I
look drunk yes those but it was suppose
a little bit of the same don't
think much of a job just
a little bit hazy something I gotta
tell you about Archie the British in
the eyes she's hot very hard to say the
hottest dog in TOWIE has stolen him
and what some of. What she's
doing here I thought it was just
not enough do you still and she came back
I was still single ONE TIME NOW what are
you not now going to take him for the you
know he would never make it to the car
you're going to bed you've got
a lot of explaining the ladle waited until
you got to get rid of him right away now
he sees the kiss and then see her friend
on the scene of course since the dog is
a witness to what you've been up
to Little Night. Oh he could only.
If he only would.
Your. Wife has. Been murdered twice
the
in.
The you you.
Would. The all nice and cozy on
ships you like it here oh actually. Yes
the police on the radio.
Trying to sell police the of.
The all you child.
Are already. To see you had.
The same. Day or yours.
Was not
a boy. Trust although. She
is right at.
The moment I don't want to so I.
Just get my hands on.
The you. Can. Always you will have.
Your home again Mr Dudley He added The
dog loved me i mean i got locked out the
door swung close to the
window. Wondering about
I didn't want to wake up. I didn't have
a generation for others don't suppose I
would've won the belt for sure certainly Mr
Harrison I don't know.
The case.
For War No for our reporting and
nothing oh. I'm not man as you are
the same again. Yeah that's
him. Not listening anymore.
The you see the
if you say.
If you. Say hello.
Just. I wake up and it's
for you I'm fine you know
I'm
a nice. Hello to you. Yes. Yes
I know thank you. So poleaxed tell me
a little funny.
Little bit of
a new. I did it don't
sound like it only you
know what are the look out of the original
If only don't sound like you did you
hook up first the light try again I was
down and be sassy. I always will not that
my name is not old it is then
very Now we all know oh.
Get back to your division Now see here if
I chill Jonathan walked in here on my own
free will to tell you I found his body would
not be crazy they only reason you are
not in
a straitjacket right now is on the causeway
don't have want to empty that all my
study for years and of course I never heard
of any steps getting knocked off twice
in two different places. I am
a child Orion. How much ironic you show
it. It's killing the blade
now to know that me
maybe you are not as crazy as you are
saying that what you said we find there are
right only it's not yours I tell you what
it is I was as close to him as I am to
you I know him anywhere it was chosen and
backed up with the extra hole and pray
that Jonah found ice in the morning I'm
incensed that him yes. Poor fellow
What about this one. I never saw him before
this one's John Nash the first one of
the L.A.
To play the same one we just found dead
now as I say if you really want to kill
Jonas just before you got that Jonah showed
up at nine thirty on the stand he him
might have murdered me too an oversight
he could have been like that. You want to
tell us now how come I went to the drugstore
towers and found guilty what you want
to say about about
a dog I told you just like you want to
tell us his apartment the ad in the paper
and then the other one. This one Don't get
me that the happy happy poet Yes I have
to do is raise if you can or
even. Watch cat watch bracelet
watch dog Doc ears back shadow but I
sit back right front for. I said no
we shame and show tout what it outweighs
the bad guys are seen as hotel gotta know
what that track style towers.
Oh my. Better just to the
same in this hotel if I found
a body as the drunk phone towers
through this said. Maybe this was.
You know what. I am.
Already.
Only. Just.
Now that's what I call it charmingly
furnished right. Job calling me home
my wife so I bought an anniversary present
I didn't tell her the truth figuring I'd
return the dog however and ran away Byron
out of. For the first ad was Jonas and
he's dead then this Gilly when I saw
it was Jonas he said. He's dead.
And now these other two Oh
a little and I don't see any more I
had no no daddy always ish NO ME WHAT
back Freddy I tell you I don't know
probably all and I think it had
a falling out and getting like Jonah show
off then Jonas I mean Fat Freddy's not
getting off even the score so good he
turns right around and I just. But so did
perfect Friday this fine actor I don't get
it done in ten you know I just says to
me what do you know about him nothing on
this he turns to three or four days ago
for three months and anybody
measured him yes oh.
I watch it all across all said he heard an
argument and then two quick charge kill
shot two batteries challenged my hero I
always missed I want what out that he said
he saw two guys to me two different guys
after the shots well why didn't the very
fact that fire was not I'm afraid here but
up till I met those two fellows but they
don't fit
a minute no they don't know the dog
what about that argy bargy the dog.
Oh he told me of done it and when he
was with me he was with my wife as
a connection there's got to be so that's
what I've been telling you No I don't get
hot in the kid's identities.
Oh my my wife my Katie
she's in danger of going to what show you
so you know what you see in the young man
she's probably going to know what you
guys are getting Who got you Oh don't be
so anxious for the dog's name please you
wait until you know how do you think oh.
Well. You see.
Shadows.
Were rule. The
show you save. The world.
OK maybe you. Already.
Cash.
Watch this. Final total mug
shot of the so-called adage no dice.
And that is the stuff she had on the
banks why do you. Think I pull
anything do you tie it up pass.
It on your head. High that in the battle
royale. That I'm sure you'll be back.
But she.
Got her job where if you. Were you
you know what I want my wife.
I don't know what the question
is still. Trying to answer you.
But I want to thank. You so
much yes I wish I'd thought of.
So you know I think it's just
plain dog always if I was
a couple of plays. I was very
sure that you saw it but I
was right I wasn't me and I see you know
why you watch him and you don't worry for
. The day so if you put what you saw
is what I thought I said but you know
what I say the right to talk to you
to show you I was going to tell you going
from zero back turn to hearing Jay OK I
just want you. Oh you know Bunny.
Are you sure you're all I want the cheers
and the it's just the words it's the
right to just one of the areas I know you
could have done whatever he just didn't
come out and go oh that's God Again
I didn't give him the job. He said
you know what I don't what you
what am I. Doing what you mean.
So much for you. If you're
sure that the whole.
Pay me when you came up here
you did this you see. The
guy two dollars a day you want to
a new phase of thrift So it's
getting cold. They hate you.
Do. Oh de I don't know who already has oh.
Believe me she got
a long ways to milk. You know I actually
knew the the.
So I get to the point the Do You Want
You must want to me to heaven if you
want to please have
a little good to them but you probably won't
need to simplify to see the movies had
more money than he knows what to do think
it doesn't. Do you know I said that what
he said no what do you want to thank you
for it he but I can see if the man gave
it to you wanted it to happen we just told
you that all you want you'll never get
one hundred thousand dollars you that were
given to going to the do you pick on him
let us get you some of. Those friends
what do you think is going to go to.
You said I want to see the money you.
Even if how was yours you couldn't spend
enough it's money in here in Boston what
can I do because it's counterfeit. Count
if it's phony all babies are as phony as
Mother's false teeth starting at anybody's
mother is supposed to be living in
a smudge on Lincoln's B.S.
But about twenty notice anything odd about
Andrew Jackson hello carefully at his
nose. I don't you say so he's got
a cold the don't get it the guy was
a man give it to you since I'm going to
tell you what I want any eccentric great
human here deliver me full interesting
unsuspecting growing doesn't even though
that's what makes him
eccentric. This is my oh my.
God you know tell him yes what I can graduate
you know what I mean about this money
oh. I made it to me. I
managed it I was on before
my husband says it's all counterfeit. I
guess he is phony lady any idiot even
trying one could tell that up Go Daddy
what you specialize in Marnie moment side
and all like that why don't you take this
to the proper authorities because I'm
convinced this is some guy who want to use
murder that is so I could oh. Oh Archie
So I wouldn't want anything to do you talking
about when you got it shut up and not
interrupt and out of the day when I'm
interrupting he's writing about I wouldn't
but so the evidence that just happened
while you don't know anything about this
could have been much more than
please let me explain. Things.
To
a little all began when I
had. To go I had gone. We
put in the money to go home the shit outta
here are you on the impression that your
husband or just that is so up for you
as in the first repression threats I am
certain he did darling went but according
to your husband's testimony that no such
thing he says your husband says that he
that dog followed him to your husband's
home he's
a dog was or is there something you forgot
it was your random version ready your
husband forgot not the dog notifying
never forgot the key talking about it
just told you. But I didn't
forget the look I tried to tell
you last night but I was the grocery
cards in our team has been said to Happy
Anniversary Dolly yet it was in Argentina
you know it was the anxiety that Archie
picked it up to after I wrote it to put
it in the box with an icon I thought I
don't want to go down but you know I bought
it for you know the general idea but
not as I started to look and this isn't
your book to showcase in the story in which
I made up
a car you were going to take the people
home to happen to know that lady. Why
the part about it but why did you pick
her to show them the scale and it was
because she was without
a dollar at the top why was journalist
killed standing by the specifics of this
video told what about those other two men
murdered in the hotel was shot I don't
know if I tell you but tell
me to tell you the she's
a monetary settlement economy
yourself a little go home now
a couple more she simply he's he's got it
I just did it last the cigarette it was
the right time you know he did what he
wanted was that he ran away to win like he's
God you know today is Saturday don't you
understand that those funds are the
subject of the dog shit you think you are.
Perv. Oh didn't break your heart she.
Said oh you fine all that
handle his. Money oh why
oh why should.
I ask you money.
Although Catherine Denny live here don't
move I've seen already filmed like this
here heard some guy but it was me the
chippy looking character he was the you say
thank you he I'm. Sure
you're here why don't you.
Take just the same Mr you cut
me out of my wallet. The the.
Six bucks that your reward for bodies
Cajuns board dusty money that he beat me
to the ability to check
the lady when she's got.
The books Thank you. No one
knows. Me.
Like you.
Darling darling.
You big boom our head you. Who. I
couldn't take another night
a mother snoring. So
rewarding but maybe just out of him he
should join Matteis So I talked to the head
of the church and I can tell you that the
feeling for hard to get an extra night
we've got the whole house all
Jewish settlement. So how do you
do you know that we love her
good to look at it let's go for
a walk or something you know
what I like a bit more what does
a lot of you know well let's go to
movies to try to make sure the old one
the guy got on and enjoy the new.
Old kid
a little emotional Well you ought to fix
that you know who you know my friends the
middle game the money yeah but.
If you don't want to do you go to
the shops mighty Chad and go get it
yes tell you show him what I didn't get
to hear today what do you see so I don't
know what's been treated by just an old
house but yes darling I'm going to just sit
right here quietly He's my lady be like Him
He took hours yes sir that is startling
and don't always take me to get my
haircut to. The guy who said that if
you get
a lawyer you go through as quick when you
brought it up police least yes police and
even if we see optional wrong I've
got all the time for all good.
The did you know what you.
Thought. And I did. Oh I'll say Oh.
The only way you. Get it.
I tell you we brought the money to the
police I had to cheat you may get you in the
past
a hundred G.'s the do you mean the
I'm going to I thought I was in
the needed photo maybe you know I said
I'm going to the yes no no she stormed
I saw the yes I didn't think it
was the money but your life and
I thank. You darling that. I
did not yet know that you've
already made the life I should
let So I don't you have
a choice my sis So you saw you safe but
if you don't we could have the money and
the stuff too let's meet.
You too because I was still
supposed to you know folks Yep you.
Do you owe you. Oh what Katie.
Told P.S.
I'm not counting my wife I largely.
You know don't you mean to say you'll
be right all working so.
Yes. My very.
Good evening Captain Daniel
Holmes you're not the police. For
a lot. Of their years here you can
take and welcome. So far the.
Strangers to me they shot
each other. My wife.
For that money some guy had
a lot of debt that hard work so you put
your money on how much I would pay what I
do have. Given you got
a. Funny. Little Boy I.
Just open your mouth
open your. Little one.
Oh. Yes thanks for.
Already I look around and I say.
Nice assortment never mind.
OK You know you. Don't tell me what
shall we watch about five grand
a piece you find five grand that way.
It's. Bring up so many
sort of. Pieces that push
a deal that it makes the ballot
short a white person out
a point you know nice as you're
cleaning up at your door.
Maybe oh. He's.
Going to. Give me the bill. Is going to
a little wrong. That we
finally rounded up the
others are gay Furthermore as a result
of the tearing on our band single I had
a chapter by the Fairless Mr Oh Danny.
Getting it over until I walked away after I
had glimmers rewards of
a new poster for the OP. Ed on the line
you can find who has and to begin to want
to continue to sure. Boy am I
going to pay income taxes share.
Out. These two were the
ones that put me in
a higher bracket OK You shall kill hero
you. Want to charge so you can already.
I don't even see them you did to my aunt
just now you got to post what are you
talking five. Ft.
Four ins with the new. One is
unlike you I'm going to let
me stick watching I spoke to tell
you all you need to commit so I
know you see.
The the. Church.
When you show them to.
I and why shouldn't he in his own house.
To know. The yes.
You
should you. Do you see what.
You see I knew you said I don't know
you saw.
You so don't you say.
I'm done I'll show
you. You
.